edrawsoft.com 2018-02-20

# Edraw Privacy

Edraw Software is committed to protecting your privacy.

### Privacy

We will only collect your personal information for defined purposes. We do not distribute or share your personal information beyond what is strictly necessary to fulfill our obligations to you. Edraw Software will not sell your personal information in any manner whatsoever.

### What information do we collect? What do we use it for?

When you place an order on our website, your full name, email address, mailing address, phone number, credit card number, and credit card expiration date will be required. The information is used to complete the transaction and help us provide better support and services to you. But Only the Digital River collects your credit card information. Edraw Collects your full name, email address, mailing address and phone number.

### Cloud Privacy

Edraw cloud is intended to offer a stable, reliable and convenient cloud storage service for all Edraw registered users, and committed to keeping your data secure. All your data will be stored safely on Alicloud. (Alicloud is one of the largest cloud service company in the world which belongs to the internationally renowned Alibaba Group - who has been a nasdaq-listed company for years.) Nobody could access to your data except yourself. 

You are responsible for keeping your password and other login details confidential. We will not ask you for your password except when you log in to the website.

Edraw Cloud will also keep your personal information safe. We have implemented physical, technical and administrative safeguards reasonably designed to protect your personal information from unauthorized access and disclosure. We will only collect your personal information for defined purposes. We do not distribute or share your personal information beyond what is strictly necessary to fulfill our obligations to you. Edraw Software will not sell your personal information in any manner whatsoever. 

### About Cookies

In order to better understand what services are valuable to our customers, we use "cookies". A cookie is a small text file that a Website writes to your hard drive. Cookies also can determine other information, such as the daily visitors to our website and the pages of the site most frequently visited. Cookies are unique and can only be read by the server that assigns them. They cannot be executed as code or deliver viruses.

You can change the settings in your browser to prevent cookies if you do not want to have a cookie set when you visit our website. However, by doing so, you may not have full access to all the web pages.

### Secure E-Commerce

Our secure e-commerce website was powered by [RegNow](http://www.regnow.com/) and Avangate, the division of Digital River, based in the USA.

Digital River has taken great precautions to ensure that your card information is kept a secret. RSA security is generally regarded as on of the strongest available. Please visit their site for more information. With these security precautions in place, your order is at least as secure, if not more than it is when you call in a phone order to a mail-order software house.
